<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour Guide</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>
    <string name="top_sights">Top Sights</string>
    <string name="events">Events</string>
    <string name="eiffel_tower">Eiffel Tower</string>
    <string name="eiffel_desc">Landmark 324-m-high 19th-century tower</string>
    <string name="louvre">The Louvre</string>
    <string name="louvre_desc">Landmark art museum with vast collection</string>
    <string name="arc">Arc de Triomphe</string>
    <string name="arc_desc">Triumphal arch and national monument</string>
    <string name="disney">Disneyland Paris</string>
    <string name="disney_desc">Iconic amusement park with themed rides</string>
    <string name="notre">Notre-Dame de Paris</string>
    <string name="notre_desc">Iconic gothic church with literary link</string>
    <string name="event_bastille">Bastille Day</string>
    <string name="bastille_date">14 July</string>
    <string name="event_fete">Fete de la Musique</string>
    <string name="fete_date">21 June</string>
    <string name="event_festival">Festival d\'Avignon</string>
    <string name="festival_date">July</string>
    <string name="event_nice">Nice Carnival</string>
    <string name="nice_date">February</string>
    <string name="event_tour">Tour de France</string>
    <string name="tour_date">July</string>
    <string name="event_plages">Paris Plages</string>
    <string name="plages_date">July</string>
    <string name="restaurant_baratin">Le Baratin</string>
    <string name="baratin_desc">When Paris chefs want to unwind they head for this little wine bar in Belleville where Argentine-born self-taught chef Raquel Carena serves up some of the most deeply satisfying food in Paris. The chalkboard menu changes constantly, but Carena loves offal and fish, and her palate favors tart and sweet-and-sour flavors, as seen in recent dishes like mackerel tartare with smoked vinegar, tuna steak with black cherries, and rabbit and mushroom ragout with red-wine sauce.</string>
    <string name="restaurant_desnoyer">La Table d\'Hotes de Hugo Desnoyer</string>
    <string name="desnoyer_desc">According to star butcher Hugo Desnoyer, who supplies many of Paris’s Michelin starred chefs with their meat, the world’s best steak is a sirloin of Limousin beef. “It has the perfect texture and an intense mineral-rich and herbaceous flavor that echoes the pastures where the cattle is raised,” says Desnoyer. Flash-seared and sprinkled with fleur de sel, it’s served medium-rare at his two restaurants, since the French think well-done meat is a sacrilege.</string>
    <string name="restaurant_arlots">Les Arlots</string>
    <string name="arlots_desc">The neighborhood near the Gare du Nord train station is nondescript, and this tiny bistrot a vins packs its clients in like sardines. No one minds the humdrum location or the crowding, though, because it serves some of the best and most reasonably priced French comfort food in Paris. Chef Thomas Brachet’s chalkboard menu changes daily but offers an irresistible mix of contemporary dishes — like a salad of green beans, apricots, speck, and fresh almonds and John Dory meuniere with vegetable accras (beignets) — and traditional ones, which may include langoustines with homemade mayonnaise and the best homemade sausage and potato puree in Paris.</string>
    <string name="best_restaurants">Best Restaurants</string>
    <string name="place_copenhagen">Copenhagen</string>
    <string name="copenhagen_desc">Copenhagen holds a special place in our hearts. We weren\'t there for long, but each day was a treat to explore this enchanting city.  With Tivoli Gardens, Nyhavn, The Little Mermaid and an endless stream of canals, Copenhagen definitely deserves to be named one of Europe\'s most beautiful cities.</string>
    <string name="place_venice">Venice</string>
    <string name="venice_desc">Many people don\'t love Venice, but we think it is because they have never stayed there long enough.  We would watch cruise lines and bus tours come in for a day and zip right back out before they had a chance to really explore Venice.  We spent six days total in Venice and loved getting lost in its back alleys, taking boat trips through the canals and enjoying quiet drinks on a bistro terrace.</string>
    <string name="place_prague">Prague</string>
    <string name="prague_desc">We had often heard that Prague was beautiful and when we first laid eyes on her, she didn\'t disappoint.  Yes it is busy and crowded, but if you step out of the main trail, you\'ll find quiet spots to grab a bite or a pint.  If you wake up early and walk around the city, you will have it all to yourselves.  Dave and I were amazed to see that people didn\'t really get started until after well after 9:00 am giving us plenty of time to enjoy the beautiful architecture in private.</string>
    <string name="similar_places">Similar Places</string>
</resources>
